# Elena Papazova

## Software Engineer

• Blv. Partizanski Odredi 33, 1000 Skopje, North Macedonia 🖂 elena\_papazova@hotmail.com

🕒 +38977926520 📞 +38977926520 🛮 in elena-papazova 👩 Spirit-78

#### **Profile**

Hello! I am a computer science student working on my bachelor's degree. I've dabbled in most of the popular programming languages, but find the scripting languages especially easy and natural for me to code in.

I primarily work with serverless solutions on AWS Cloud, utilizing React.js and Typescript, both frontend and Node.js backend. Other than that, I also have some experience with Google Cloud and Firebase/Firestore.

I consider myself very adaptable, always eager and open to working with, and learning new languages and tech stacks. Feel free to checkout my LinkedIn for a more complete list of all the languages and stacks I've worked with.

### **Education**

#### Bachelor's Degree,

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering 09/2017 — present | Skopje, North Macedonia

## **Professional Experience**

Miracle Mill, Software Engineer

01/2022 – present | Skopje, North Macedonia Fullstack developer, working with AWS services and cloud solutions.

Exelerate, Software Engineer

04/2021 – 11/2021 | Skopje, North Macedonia Fullstack developer, working mostly on serverless backend with REST calls, technologies such as Elasticsearch, Stripe, Docusign etc...

Skills	
JavaScript/Typescript	• • • • •
Node.js	• • • • •
Amazon Web Services (AWS)	• • • • •
React	• • • • •
HTML/CSS	• • • •
Python	• • • • •
Languages	
English Full working proficiency (C2)	• • • •
<b>German</b> Elementary proficiency (A2)	••••
Macedonian	• • • • •

#### **Certificates**

0 0 0 0

Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner ☑ Credential ID: VW1M6VVBHNRQ1P9K

Other Miscellaneous Certificates 72

## **Projects**

## Highlighted projects I've worked on:

- Prometheus Agri □
- Hammarby □
- iESE ☑

Native (C2)

Beginner (A1)

Spanish

• My own CV